[ music ]]
What is Slashjay?
Slashjay is a FNaF fan comic
that takes place after Security Breach.
It follows Gregory,
who is living at the Pizzaplex with the
(now fixed and not murderous)
animatronics.
After Freddy begins acting up,
Gregory becomes determined
to figure out what's wrong with him.
Eventually leading him down the rabbit hole
that is Fazbear Entertainment
and the horrors that come with it.
Some of the main characters are
Gregory
Vanessa A.
Glamrock Freddy
Michael Afton
Charlie Emily
Evan Afton
and more.
Slashjay is full of brainrot,
and, at its core, is am service
so keep that in mind.
Slashjay may contain disturbing or sensitive material
content and trigger warnings will be applied when able
but discretion is advised.
Thank you for watching
[ music ]]
Missing
Cassidy Williams
Age twelve, 4'10 female
missing Jeremy Walker H 12 male
missing Fritz Walker a 6 male
missing Susie Crystal H 10 female
missing Gabriel Harriet a 13 male
and I do hope you may join us
sav̶e̴ ̸ th̷̦͓̎̅̈e̸̢̡͍̪̱̯͂̌͗̒m̶̥̤̀
you c̶̡̥̗̹̯̱̒̑͂̄͐̓a̵̞̝̻̥͙̭͇̿͗̓͒̓͂̽n̸̤̝̰͎̜̲̥̈̾̎͆̿̒͂'̷̨̛͔́̅́t̴̢̢̛̠̣͊̐̏͐̈́͠